Whenever I talk to other people how to do Future Authoring writing plan
Usually encounter delays
This is not surprising
Because it is already difficult
But the more problem is that they will think:
"I don't know how to start writing"
"I will do a bad job"
"I don't like this job"
"I want to be perfect"
"Wait until I have time to do it"
One reason you might not want to do it
Not to mention there are five reasons
So I suggest people
Do something at will
Even if there is only fragmentary time or a bad job
Because you can do it
I always tell my students when discussing master thesis with students
Write a draft first, even if it is bad
But we will have a short discussion first
Because they don't think I really think like this
Because that sounds cliché
But not a cliché
It's just like...
You are a bad writer
But if someone points a gun to your head and says:
"You must complete your hundreds of pages of draft by next Monday"
"Otherwise I will blow your head"
"I don't care how bad you write"
Then you will sit down and write obediently
What i want to say is
When you have a draft, you can modify it
You can revise the draft repeatedly
That's the most important and valuable and what you need
You need a first draft of your own but not so good
Jung has such a concept
Developed from comedy
Just
"The liar is the pioneer of the savior"
This is one thing i learned from
It sounds abnormal
Hard to believe this is true
The catastrophe clown fool in satire
The fool is the pioneer of the savior
why?
Because you are a fool in a new field
So if you don’t want to be a fool
You can't start a new job
You can't start a new job, you won't make progress
and so
Willing to be a fool
There is a way to change
This is also a kind of humility
If you are about to start your life
Your first job can be bad
You will get smarter as you move forward
This is the point
Something attracted you that's what we are going to say today
Maybe the stars that Geppetto is looking forward to are completely wrong
But at least that's the stars
At least it appeared
At least it made him move forward
So you say when you are attracted to something
Or interested in something
Then you start to think should I do this
the answer is
"If I don't do it, there are other things I can do"
"If it was a wrong decision?"
This is the wrong idea!
Don't worry you don't know anything yet
You are just about to take a difficult step, aren't you
You have to move, you can’t stay where you are
I have seen many people
They said: "I am 40 years old but I never knew what to do"
This is not a good phenomenon
That's bad
You might think
There is a form of literature reminiscent of those who are very depressed
When they remember the past
About the things they didn't do
And the mistakes they committed
This is also worth thinking about
There is a kind of compensatory error
This is a compensation you try after you make a mistake
Actually you think: Okay, I want to do this
But you are not very good at making a lot of mistakes
It’s like: "What if I’m more focused?"
"I shouldn't be this stupid anymore"
You can learn from the results
and so
You follow your desire
But you were like a blind man at first
You are not sure where the end is, you are afraid to move forward
But you decide to step out
When you start to step out
You can get shimmer and direction
Because those past experiences will tell you
When you push yourself out of the comfort zone
Then you find that the direction you are going is wrong
Ten steps forward
Then you think "it doesn't seem to be here"
"Not there, it should be here"
You found Liu Yinghua bright another village
You move on and you will find
When you continue or change direction
Like in the Egyptian desert
You find that the brilliance you seek is also moving
It's not a permanent thing
When you move toward it, it moves with it, and it leads you forward.
You would say: Am I moving towards an ideal country?
The answer is: no, you don't know anything
Only know when you reach the goal
But you might have that amazing glance
When you continue
You will become more and more aware
And this will be a continuous process
Your move will look like this
Interestingly
All these transitions you face, the blow you face
"Gosh! I'm in trouble"
I seem to have died once, but recovered a little from it
Like a phoenix on fire, reborn from every turn
It's torture
It's just like
You have walked 20 miles
But in fact you are only 3 miles ahead of your real goal
Just 3 miles
When you are still in place, you are in a regressive state
You can't stand still
Because the whole world moves forward
If you stand still, you will be left behind
If you don’t move forward, you will only regress
And this is more in line with the Matthew effect:
"Those who have everything will be awarded more"
"Take everything from those who have nothing"
This is a vigilance
Don't stay where you are
After you move forward hard
Lessons learned at every turn
Then you stop making such fatal mistakes
Maybe you will find a more suitable direction in the end if you can realize
This will already be your journey although not yet
May be worse than this
Or some flaws
But it doesn't matter
When you move forward
You will find by yourself
Maybe partly because the world is made up of information
If you dig
He will tell you something
You will get and be ready